good afternoon, good yes, how are you doing
добрый день добрый да как там у вас дела
normally your crumbs don’t send to us
нормально ваших крош не отправляет к нам
the same but where
тому же а где
near mariupol he gave pronto don’t
под мариуполем подарил pronto не
cut it don’t cut it don’t sit so calmly
обрежьте подарил так спокойно не сидели
brother
брат
we see it’s a pretty dude in civilian
видим это довольно чувак по гражданке
life the dachshund doesn’t tell the
такса не рассказывает
game just [ __ ] play it found that
игры просто [__] неё играть нашел ту
department can  Yes, and what’s so bad shhshhsh
отдел может да а что так плохо шшшш
found that the department you are well-allowed
нашел то отдел вы хорошо допустимый
help field, here’s how to calculate for
подмогу поле вот а как высчитать ради
what you are fighting for what you are dying for
чего вы воюете ради чего вы умираете
to [ __ ] you so I’m not near
чтоб тебя захуярить так я ж не возле
Mariupol, Ivan surnames scam far,
мариуполя иван фамилий скам далеко
that is, it turns out look you will die
то есть получается смотри ты сдохнешь
in order for Kadyrov to take off  tick tock
для того чтоб кадыров снял tick tock
it’s true that Kadyrov’s words will be your
правда вот к кадырову слова будет твоей
mother’s funeral, which is how you
маме похоронка который вот как ты
feel about the oder,
относишься к одеру
don’t [ __ ] start it,
ты [__] не заводи
it plays great why don’t I
прекрасно играется почему мне почему не
start a topic about the coder, look, that is, to a
заводи тему про кодера смотри то есть к
hole in and a hole there, the title was awarded to the
дыра в так и дыру там звание вручили
general for what for something so  he throws you
генерала за что за то чтоб тебя бросает
somewhere into battle,
куда-то в бой
so you are a Russian guy there, and
так тебя там русского парня а
Kadyrov takes off and some and got a
кадыров снимает и каких-то и получил
general, so the Chechens, in short, I will
генерала так чеченцы короче буду там
collect all your  these
собирать все ваши эти
buns are rewards, and you will
плюшки награды так а вам похоронки будут
receive funeral sh, there is one who will
приходить sh таки есть который выиграет
win bonuses for himself, and for you, specifically,
себе бонусы а тебе вот конкретно тебе
what will happen to you from this war
что будет от этой войны
wins in
выигрывает в
peace and quiet.
тишине и покое .
but we will erase
а вот мы сотрем
for the sake of, for the sake of what you are fighting,
ради-ради ради чего вот вы воюете вот
that’s what’s in you specifically and you will be
что в тебе конкретно и тебе будет
for the sake of what you want to achieve a
ради чего что вы хотите добиться
lot of money that kind of money, don’t
огромные деньги такие деньги вы же не
tell me, but I will pay 500,000
смешите по но мне оплатит 500000 чего
rubles, up to 500 thousand rubles,
рублей до 500 тысяч рублей не платят
the sky officers do not pay  it’s
офицерский состав sky не получается все
impossible not to tell everything 100 thousand rubles,
не рассказывать 100 тысяч рублей
look, it just turns out that you came
смотри просто получается вот ты приехал
from some
из какого-то своего